2bstores.com 2018-11-22

# Privacy and Security | bebe

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS.**

## PRIVACY & SECURITY

At bebe we recognize and respect your privacy when you use our website or any of our mobile applications. Our privacy policy describes how we collect, use and may share the information we collect on our websites and mobile apps (collectively ?bebe.com?). To demonstrate our commitment, we have developed the privacy policy outlined below. If you have any questions about this policy, or the content or practices of our website, we encourage you to contact us.

## COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION & USE

When you visit bebe.com, with the help of our third-party authorized agents, we collect information (such as your mobile device unique identification number, IP address, domain name, browser type, broad geographical information, site-navigation pattern, etc.) to improve our website and to refine our marketing campaigns and promotions. If you log into your bebe.com account from different devices, we will include your device identification to your account automatically so that you can move easily from your computer to your mobile device. We do not gather any personally identifying information about you when you visit this site, unless you choose to provide such information to us.

We collect certain personally identifiable information when you sign in to the bebe website; create an account for online shopping; register with clubbebe; participate in a contest, promotion or survey; or request other services that require information, registration or subscription. This information may include your name, billing address, phone number, email address, credit card number and expiration date, a user name and password, your birth date, your driver?s license number and state of issuance to verify your identity, and any other information you voluntarily provide. We also keep a record of your product interests and purchases online and in our stores, and automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser (including your IP address, bebe cookie information and the page you requested).

We may collect location information from our mobile app users, if you permit it. You can control making geolocation information available to us by visiting your mobile device?s settings for the application. When you install our apps on a mobile device, you can choose to receive push notifications, which are messages an app sends you on your mobile device, even when the app is not active. You can turn off notifications by visiting your mobile device?s ?settings page? for external applications. We may use your information according to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use in effect at the time of use. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or statements regarding our privacy practices with respect to this Site. We may use aggregated data (independent of any personal identifiers) for research and commercial purposes. This information includes what areas our users visit most frequently and what services they access most often. This information helps us develop a better site that is more useful and accessible to you.

We may use your personally identifiable information internally for our general commercial purposes including, among other things, to offer our own, our affiliates? or third-party products and services that we think you may find of interest. We may use your email address to contact you to respond to your inquiries, provide updates or newsletters, or to provide information on products or services to you. You can elect not to receive promotional emails from us either by ?unsubscribing? to an email you receive or by contacting us as indicated below.

## DISCLOSING YOUR INFORMATION

bebe may share aggregate site and demographic information (such as age, gender, types of products or services purchased and bebe.com navigation, usage and page view). Such information does not identify any individual person and allows us to provide a more enjoyable online shopping experience.

bebe may reveal personally identifiable information about you to unaffiliated third parties: (1) if you request or authorize it; (2) if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) if the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) if the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); (5) if the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or (6) as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

## LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

Please be aware that our site may contain links to other sites hosted by third parties. bebe does not control and is thus not responsible for the content or privacy practices and policies of such other sites.

## HOW YOU CAN ACCESS, CHANGE OR DELETE YOUR INFORMATION

You may, at any time, access and update or remove your personal information by contacting Client Services via email or by clicking on Contact Us from any page on bebe.com. You may access and update your account information by logging into the My Account page. In addition, if you prefer not to receive information from us through email, you may opt out of receiving bebe emails by clicking the ?unsubscribe? link at the bottom of any bebe email that you have received. If you prefer not to receive information from us through regular mail (for example, catalogs and direct mail promotions), please send us an email or call Client Services at 877-bebe-777 (877-232-3777). Please note that it may take up to 3 weeks for your request to become effective. Thereafter, when you make purchases, we may still send you an email confirmation and may need to contact you by phone, email or regular mail if we have other questions regarding your order. If for any reason you continue to receive email or regular mail from bebe after following the steps above, please contact Client Services immediately and we?ll be happy to assist you. For general information about bebe stores, inc. please visit the About bebe page.

## SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

Our goal is to provide you with a safe and convenient online shopping experience. We use reasonable technical, administrative and physical measures to protect information contained in our system against misuse, loss or alteration. When placing an order online, your information is transmitted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the information being transferred to us. To check the security of your connection, view the lower corner of your browser window as you place your order. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active and the server is secure. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from ?http? to ?https.? Information that you provide to us is not secured during transmission unless the URL address contains ?https?.

We are not responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any non-public information that you provide us. Any information you prove in the course of reviews or ratings is publicly available. Information that you provide us by email is not encrypted.

No method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee absolute security of your information. You also play a role in protecting your information. Please safeguard your user name and password and do not share them with others. If we receive instructions using your log-in information we will consider that you have authorized the instructions.

## COOKIES

To enhance your shopping experience at bebe.com, we and our third-party authorized agents use cookies, small data files that we store on your computer?s hard drive. Rest assured, the cookies we and our partners use do not store personally identifiable information. They simply enable us to keep track of your shopping experience and your order as you shop our site. The cookies we may use on our Site include:

Session cookies: These temporary cookies expire and are automatically erased whenever you close your browser window. We use session cookies to grant our users access to content and to enable actions they must be logged in to do. For example, bebe.com uses session cookies in order to save your shopping bag information so that you can browse from page to page without losing that information. When shopping bebe.com, we recommend you use a cookie-enabled browser in order to avoid having to constantly reenter information.

Persistent cookies: These usually have an expiration date in the distant future and remain in your browser until they expire or you manually delete them. We use persistent cookies to better understand usage patterns so we can improve the site for our customers. For example, we may use a persistent cookie to associate you with your user account or to remember your choices on the Site, but this only works when cookies on our site are enabled. Cookies also enable us to monitor and maintain information about your use of our site. The information we retrieve assists us with tracking your order, improving our site design, products, services, contests, promotions and overall shopping experience.

Third party cookies: We permit limited third parties to place cookies through the Site to provide us with better insights into the use of the Site or user demographics or to provide relevant advertising to you. These third parties may collect information about a consumer?s online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our website. For example, we may utilize Google Analytics to analyze usage patterns of the Site. Google Analytics generates a cookie to capture information about your use of the Site which Google uses to compile reports on website activity for us and to provide other related services. Google may use a portion of your IP address to identify their cookie, but this may or may not be associated with any other data held by Google.

We may also permit third party service providers to place cookies through our Site to perform analytic or marketing functions. We do not control the use of such third party cookies or the resulting information and we are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. Your use of our Site will be deemed to be your consent to the placement of cookies on your computer or other device. If you prefer not to receive cookies through our Site, you can set your browser to either reject all cookies, to allow only ?trusted? websites to set them, or to accept only those cookies from those sites you are currently on. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our Site and use it.

If you refuse cookies, this may limit system performance and may even cause certain features of the Site to malfunction or not to work at all. You can learn more about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies).

We do not use technology that recognizes a ?do-not-track? signal from your web browser.

## POLICY OF YOUNG CHILDREN

bebe is concerned about the privacy of young children, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13 years of age. bebe does not sell products for purchase by children.

## YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of bebe stores, inc. who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address:

bebe stores, inc.  
Legal Department  
400 Valley Dr.  
Brisbane, CA 94005

## CHANGES TO POLICY

bebe reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove any portion of bebe.com or these Policies, in whole or in part, at any time. Changes to these Policies will be effective when posted. You agree to review these Policies periodically to be aware of any changes. Your continued use of bebe.com after any changes to these Policies are posted will be considered acceptance of those changes.

## EFFECTIVE DATE

This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 10th, 2016

Back to Top
